let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the capitol of Massachusetts?",
    answer: "Boston",
    options: [
      "Sacramento",
      "Maryland",
      "Boston",
      "Chicago"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the capitol of California?",
    answer: "Sacramento",
    options: [
      "Boston",
      "Phoenix",
      "Atlanta",
      "Sacramento"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the capitol of Florida?",
    answer: "Tallahassee",
    options: [
      "Boise",
      "Springfield",
      "Tallahassee",
      "Topeka"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the capitol of Maine?",
    answer: "Augusta",
    options: [
      "Boston",
      "Saint Paul",
      "Jackson",
      "Augusta"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the capitol of Ohio?",
    answer: "Columbus",
    options: [
      "Columbus",
      "Salem",
      "Pierre",
      "Austin"
    ]
  },
     {
     numb: 6,
     question: "What is capitol of Pennsylvania?",
     answer: "Harrisburg",
     options: [
       "Bismarck",
       "Concord",
       "Harrisburg",
       "Helena"
     ]
 },

 {
  numb: 7,
  question: "What is the capitol of Nebraska?",
  answer: "Lincoln",
  options: [
    "Lincoln",
    "Boston",
    "Lansing",
    "Frankfort"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 8,
  question: "What is the capitol of Kansas ?",
  answer: "Topeka",
  options: [
    "Boise",
    "Topeka",
    "Helena",
    "Raleigh"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 9,
  question: "What is the capitol of New Jersey?",
  answer: "Trenton",
  options: [
    "Concord",
    "Kursk",
    "Albany",
    "Trenton"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 10, 
  question: "What is the capitol of Wyoming?",
  answer: "Cheyenne",
  options: [
    "Richmond",
    "Pierre",
    "Cheyenne",
    "Moscow"
  ]
}

];